# **Brian Price**

(000) 000-0000

brian.price@student.swic.edu

### **Profile**

Experienced manager with 25 years of demonstrated ability to supervise, lead, follow and serve in all aspects of logistics management and operations while also being responsible for the training and mentorship of subordinate personnel. Currently broadening information technology skillset with enrollment in an associate degree program in Web Design at Southwestern Illinois College.

## Experience

2016-PRESENT

Full Time Student / Southwestern Illinois College, Belleville, IL

- Consistently on Dean's List with 4.0 GPA.
- Have completed classes in HTML and Advanced HTML, JavaScript/jQuery, Adobe Illustrator,
  Photo Manipulation (Photoshop) and Advanced Photoshop, and Database Management.

2013-2016

Fuels Manager / United States Air Force, Travis AFB, CA

- Managed 96 personnel providing leading customer support providing over 48 million gallons of fuel annually to assigned and transient aircraft.
- Directed inspections, operations, and upkeep of 18 fixed fuel facilities and 36 vehicles valued at \$168M maintaining a 97% in-service rate.

2010-2013

Fuels Operation Foreman / United States Air Force, Travis AFB, CA

- Managed a \$469k operations and maintenance budget in support of peacetime, contingency, and operational refueling missions.
- Coordinated with outside agencies to track and manage \$75M in infrastructure projects and audited a \$73M fuels account.

2007-2010

Protocol/Public Affairs Supervisor / United States Air Force, Lackland AFB, TX

- Planned and executed distinguished visitor tours for the Basic Military Training Operations, coordinating over 685 visits for various Air Force, Department of Defense, and community leaders.
- Prepared protocol correspondence, invitations, scripts, and seating diagrams for official functions, ceremonies and itineraries.

2006-2007

Military Training Instructor / United States Air Force, Lackland AFB, TX

- Planned, organized and directed basic and initial military training requirements.
- Determined requirements for facilities, space, equipment, visual aids and supplies to support training while monitoring the training program to ensure effective use of support items.

2005-2006

Unit Deployment Manager / United States Air Force, Ellsworth AFB, SD

- Managed readiness training and overseas temporary assignments for 112 personnel, tracking over 200 appointments monthly.
- Managed, processed, and instructed first aid and small arm weapon qualification classes.

1991-2005

Fuels Operator / Terminal Operator / United States Air Force, Various Assignments

- Responsible for the safe issue and storage of all fuel movement on installations.
- Documented discrepancies in fuel receipt quantities and maintained quality.
- Isolated off-specification product and took appropriate actions to correct problems while ensuring compliance with all safety and environmental regulations.

#### Education

Currently enrolled (expected Graduation in Spring 2020)

A.A.S Degree in Web Design / Southwestern Illinois College, Belleville, IL

Completed three semesters while on the Dean's List with cumulative 4.0 GPA.

**NOVEMBER 2016** 

B.S. in Business Administration / Columbia Southern Univ., Orange Beach, AL

Completed Bachelor's Degree in Business Administration with a focus on IT with a 4.0 GPA.

**APRIL 2009** 

A.A.S. in Instructor of Tech & Military Science / Community College of the AF, Maxwell AFB, AL

SEPTEMBER 2002

A.A.S. in Logistics / Community College of the Air Force, Maxwell AFB, AL

## Achievements/Activities

- Member of SWIC Chapter of Association for Information Technology Professionals (AITP).
- Graduated top of class for Military Training Instructor School earning Commandant's Award.
- Top 10% of Graduates for Non-Commissioned Officer School earning Distinguished Graduate award.